{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307307152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307307152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 285b6425-4e71-4ce6-8fa3-7b2d19557da1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307315679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307315679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307318550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307318550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307321996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307321996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307325408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307325408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307329952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307329952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307335644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307335644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307338902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307338902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307342742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307342742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307345701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307345701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307348873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307348873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307352133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307352132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307355389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307355389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307359136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307359136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307362026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307362026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307365179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307365179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307368584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307368584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307371310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307371310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307374578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307374578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307378075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307378075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307380879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307380878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307383708","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307383708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307386949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307386949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307390276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307390275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307393560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307393560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307399305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307399304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 2fe0db6e-7a3d-4978-9c7e-4bae520058c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307409057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307409057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307409554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307409554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307410698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307410697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" ANAFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307411078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307411077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307411750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307411749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307412158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307412157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307412901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307412900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307413685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307413685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307416867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307416866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307417369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307417368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307417649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307417648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307418118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307418118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307418856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307418855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307419568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307419568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307420380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307420379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307421073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307421073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307421335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307421335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307421959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307421959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307424762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307424762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307425223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307425223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307425996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307425995"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307427262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307427262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" KILICHOWEKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307428319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307428318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307428569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307428569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307428999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307428998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307429598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307429597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307432413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307432413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307432921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307432920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307433545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307433545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307434424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307434423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAZAA"," userResponse":" AKAZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307435247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307435247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307436201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307436200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307437144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307437143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDADISI"," userResponse":" MDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307441576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307441576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307441753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307441753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307442194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307442194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307442413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307442413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307442896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307442894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307443564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307443564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" MNYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307444829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307444828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMUONA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307447895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307447895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307448092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307448091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307448637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307448637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307450022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307450021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307450616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307450615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307452758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307452758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307453223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307453222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307453738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307453737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307454199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307454198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307454467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307454467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307455278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307455277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307457977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307457977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307459193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307459192"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307459857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307459855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307460648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307460648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307463175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307463174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307463403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307463403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307463876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307463876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307464361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307464360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" PEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307464974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307464973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307465406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307465405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307465879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307465878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307467340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307467339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307468127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307468126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307471138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307471138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307471339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307471339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307471913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307471912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307472380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307472380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307473636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307473635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307474417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307474417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307475132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307475131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307475721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307475720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307476095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307476095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307476578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307476577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307477567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307477566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307480493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307480492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307480980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307480980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307481481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307481480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307482482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307482482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKULA"," userResponse":" UNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307483355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307483354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307486577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307486576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307487173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307487172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307490465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307490464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" MWANANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307491859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307491859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIULIZE"," userResponse":" USIULIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307492490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307492490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307493191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307493190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307493650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307493650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307494195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307494194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307494866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307494866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307495342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307495342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307496444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307496444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307499375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307499374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307500058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307500058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307501055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307501054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANUNA"," userResponse":" KANUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307501507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307501507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307501989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307501988"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307502789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307502788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307506019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307506019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307506665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307506665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307507307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307507306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307508223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307508223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307509049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307509049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307510177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307510176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUATE"," userResponse":" NIFUATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307510720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307510720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307511454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307511454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307514160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307514159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307514904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307514903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAONA"," userResponse":" UTAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307515748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307515748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" AMBACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307516379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307516378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307516951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307516950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307517769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307517769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307520810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307520810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307520977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307520977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307521559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307521559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307522661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307522660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307523532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307523531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307524056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307524056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307524810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307524810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307528930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307528929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307529429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307529428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307530435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307530434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIANZI"," userResponse":" MIANZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307530940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307530939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307531858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307531857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307532348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307532347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307532900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307532899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGO"," userResponse":" KINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307533114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307533114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307533651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307533651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307536938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307536937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" ALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307537599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307537599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307537746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307537746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307538251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307538251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307538475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307538475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307539372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307539372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307540543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307540542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307541416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307541416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307541910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307541910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307543003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307543002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307546432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307546432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307547166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307547166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307548077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307548077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307548518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307548517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307549150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307549150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307549380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307549380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307549851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307549851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307552287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307552287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307552517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307552517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307553212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307553211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307554086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307554086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307554654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307554653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307554895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307554894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307555608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307555607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307556557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307556557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307557568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307557568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307560202","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307560202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307561116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307561116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307562568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307562568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKANIELEZA"," userResponse":" UKANIELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307563457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307563457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307563935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307563935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307564567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307564566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307565034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307565034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307565991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307565990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307570023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307570023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAMA"," userResponse":" INAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307570760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307570759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307571368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307571367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307572480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307572480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307572982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307572982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307573383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307573383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307574002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307574001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307574577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307574577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307575726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307575726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307576188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307576187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307576604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307576603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307579078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307579078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307579217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307579216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307579751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307579750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307580877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307580877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINAMA"," userResponse":" ALIINAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307581513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307581513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307582185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307582184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307583067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307583066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307583665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307583665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307584106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307584106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307584543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307584542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307585288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307585287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307588011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307588010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307588266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307588265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307588971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307588971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307589239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307589239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307589792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307589791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307590717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307590717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307591872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307591872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWANI"," userResponse":" KUNYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307592174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307592174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307592762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307592761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307595720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307595719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307596812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307596812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKULA"," userResponse":" ATAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307597375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307597375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307597884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307597883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307598431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307598431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307599305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307599304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307599964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307599964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307600665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307600665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJANJA"," userResponse":" MJANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307602358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307602357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," userResponse":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307602904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307602903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307603096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307603095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307603593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307603593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307604087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307604087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307604873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307604873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307607745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307607744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307607911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307607911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307608647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307608647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307609549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307609549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKITA"," userResponse":" AKAKITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307610448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307610448"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307610847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307610847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307611378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307611378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307611930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307611930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307612569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307612569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307614129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307614129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIMAMA"," userResponse":" AKASIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307614828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307614828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307615534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307615532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307616346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307616346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307617590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307617589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUTA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307618095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307618095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307619210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307619209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUTA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307621357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307621356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307622005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307622005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAE"," userResponse":" NAE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307623523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307623523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAIKAMATA"," userResponse":" AKAIKAMATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307624204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307624203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VEMA"," userResponse":" VEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307624729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307624728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307624955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307624955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307625652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307625652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307625868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307625868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307626511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307626511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307628472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307628471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUIACHIA"," userResponse":" HAKUIACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307631305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307631304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307631548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307631547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307632174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307632174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307632366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307632366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307633050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307633050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307634853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307634852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTIKA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307635670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307635669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307637566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307637565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAREFUKA"," userResponse":" IKAREFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307638724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307638723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307640165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307640164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307642572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307642571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUU"," userResponse":" PUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307644742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307644742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307645341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307645337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307646002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307646002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307646706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307646706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307646961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307646959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307647621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307647621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307650607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307650607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307650959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307650958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307651744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307651743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307652436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307652436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307653220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307653219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307654212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307654212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307655309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307655308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAMA"," userResponse":" ALIZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307655808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307655807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307656986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307656986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKOMEA"," userResponse":" KUTOKOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307657472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307657471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307658087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307658086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307661042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307661042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307661242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307661241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307661883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307661883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307663179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307663179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307663604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307663604"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307664170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307664169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307667000","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307667000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307667713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307667713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307668033","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307668032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307668654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307668652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307669677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307669677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIISHIA"," userResponse":" ILIISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307670302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307670301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307670955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307670954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307671925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307671924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307672609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307672609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307676371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307676369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIREFUKA"," userResponse":" ILIREFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307677171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307677170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307677728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307677728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307678881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307678880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" KUMUWEZESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307679658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307679658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307680382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307680382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307681486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307681486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307682293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307682292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307683187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307683187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307683290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307683290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307683727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307683726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307684314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307684314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307684866","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307684866"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307687869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307687868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307689283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307689283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307690208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307690208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307691144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307691143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307691634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307691633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307692358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307692357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307693469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307693469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307693691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307693691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307694360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307694359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307697343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307697341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307698057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307698057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307698911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307698910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307699749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307699749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307700153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307700153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307700874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307700874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONGA"," userResponse":" MIKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307701665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307701664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307701805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307701805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307702840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307702839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307703496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307703496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAIDA"," userResponse":" FAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307704103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307704102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307706623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307706622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307706739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307706739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 1f3aa433-5c5f-4486-b1fd-23b96e1bc942"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307716862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307716861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307734219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307734219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307739150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307739150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307781359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307781359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307786084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307786084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307789463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307789463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307793427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307793427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307796788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307796788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307800510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307800510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307804242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307804242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307807493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307807493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307810504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307810504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307813308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307813307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307816715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307816714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307820350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307820350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307824921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307824921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307829268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307829268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307832699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307832698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307837785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307837784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307845402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307845402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307855393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307855393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307859863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307859862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307871450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307871450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307877851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307877850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307891530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307891530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307894842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307894841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307900602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307900602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307936028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307936027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 658db076-3a8f-4a75-9920-a62944fcf376"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307947628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307947628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307951584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307951583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307953182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307953182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307957763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307957761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307959358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307959357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307963476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307963475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOMBO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307965105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307965105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307969476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307969476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307971031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307971031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHIPSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307974906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307974905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHIPSI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307976475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307976475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307981044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307981044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307982664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307982663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307987379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307987379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHUNGWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307988967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307988967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307993136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307993136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307994702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307994702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307997961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307997961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHOO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548307999511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548307999511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308004312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308004312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308006336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308006336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308006488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308006488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308119075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308119074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 95ca27fe-3e98-452e-8eba-2566079e461f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" CHAPATI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308119148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308119148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" c6bdaf0d-407e-4bd8-8cfd-4a55570b9581"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308128712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308128711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308129092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308129091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308129585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308129584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308129948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308129947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308130363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308130362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308130846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308130846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308131074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308131074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308134296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308134295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308134330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308134330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308135054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308135053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308135456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308135455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308135757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308135757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308135967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308135967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308136169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308136169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308136489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308136489"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308136722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308136720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308139991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308139990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308140400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308140399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308143036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308143036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308143257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308143257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308143465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308143465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308146988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308146987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308150735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308150734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308151766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308151766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308154556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308154556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308154946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308154946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308155439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308155439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308155789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308155789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308156198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308156198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308156680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308156679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308156907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308156906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308160101","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308160100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308160134","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308160134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308160849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308160849"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308161241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308161241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308161534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308161534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308161738","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308161738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308161931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308161931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308162245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308162245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308162472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308162472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308165210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308165209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308165305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308165305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_082138"," gameId":" 35ff398e-21cd-44bc-9caa-a6fea35d96ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}